Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Kowski. On this podcast, I talk
about what coaches, trainers, and
mentors can do to scale your businesses.
Now, today I want to talk about the very
best offers that you can run in your
business to get clients. A lot of people
have a coaching business and they want
to promote courses, they want to promote
a membership, they want to promote high
ticket. These are all great. What I have
found is that you have to really
simplify things and look at it big
picture. You are going to need to
increase your income in your coaching
business to over
$20,000 per month minimum. Okay? And if
you're making $20,000 per month, I want
you to get that to $40,000 per month. If
you're making $40,000 per month, at
every stage, we are going to 2x whatever
we're doing. And by the way, this is a
big piece of advice that I give a lot of
my clients is look at what's the most
amount of money that you have made
consistently and then double that. What
is two times that number?
And so like for instance for me in my
business um the most amount that I have
made while building coaching businesses
is we did right at $1 million in one
month in cash received. And so I would
love to be able to do something whether
it be in my business or coach somebody
to $2 million a month. That would be
huge. Uh, in my own business, the
biggest month I personally had because I
have a seven-figure business was
$160,000 cash received in one month.
Okay. So, my next goal, I want to get to
$360,000 cash received in one month. And
that's kind of the way that that that
the game works. I think sometimes we're
like, "Oh, I want to make a million
dollars. I want to make this much."
Personally, I just say, "What's the most
you've made in one month?" Because often
times things break down along month-long
cycles,
okay? 30-day cycles. And then give
yourself a goal to get to where that
biggest month you had is your new
baseline. That's the lowest amount that
you make each month. And then your goal
is to have a month where you make double
that. And what's going to happen is you
figure out what are the pieces I got to
move around to do that. And so defining
your offers, number
one, you absolutely need to
have two things.
A high ticket
offer. Okay, high ticket is something
that you sell for at least
$5500 or more. Okay, and by the way,
this can this can break down to even be
$5,500 in a year. Let's say that you
charge. It's a monthly fee, $900 a
month. I actually have an offer right
now. My incredible VIP one-on-one
experience. I just launched it and it's
$900 a month, but that breaks down to
$10,800 a year if somebody's in it for
an entire year. So, that's a high ticket
offer right there. The next offer that
comes in here is a
midt membership. Okay, this could be
anywhere from 47 to $200 a month. My
program is $200 a month for my midt
membership. And then on the bottom here,
we have low
ticket and free. Okay, so this is low
ticket and free offers. And these are
just for marketing to people to come up
to the higher tier right here. I often
find coaches and mentors, they're like,
I'm going to charge 27 bucks for a
course and I'm going to sell a thousand
of them and that's going to make me all
my money.
The practicality of you selling a
thousand of a course every single month
is a lot lower than you selling a
membership to
say a hundred people. If you have a
hundred people at $200 a month, that's
$20,000. Whereas if you have a,000
people at $20, that's $20,000. So 100
versus a,000 people, it's leverage. If
you're selling a high ticket program for
$10,000 in a month, you only need to
sell two of those. So, having your offer
stack that way is one of the most
important keys. Now, here's one of the
things that I want to talk about here.
When we're marketing, when you're
advertising out there, you are often not
going to get people to buy your mid
ticket or your high ticket just because
they found you on social media. And this
is one of the big um facads that people
have when it comes to marketing online
and building a coaching business is that
just because they have an incredibly
valuable offer, people are going to buy
it. In
fact, most people aren't even going to
buy your low ticket
offer. And that's just the case. And so
number one, the fact is is that
literally most people aren't going to
buy anything that you offer unless you
can learn how to persuade people that
it's worth their time. So that's where
low ticket and low tier comes from is
something for free that they can sign up
for to connect with you, to watch you on
video. And we use a combination of video
sales letters. We use a combination of
webinars, pre-recorded webinars to be
able to do this. Once somebody's on my
email list, then I'm able to loop them
around to my podcast, to my YouTube
channel to be able to connect with me
that way. So, I want you to just look
big picture here, and I want to simplify
this out for you. I want you to get it
out of your mind that people are just
going to find you on the internet and
become a client.
of your coaching program or buy your
course and that's going to make you a
bunch of
money. Sure, that could be the case.
Some people might do that, but you're
not going to make the kind of money that
you're wanting to make at that level.
Okay? To make the kind of money that
you're wanting to make, you need to have
something that connects with people on a
much deeper level. And that becomes
these free and low ticket offers that
people sign up for because then if
you're running advertising campaigns,
you can generate leads with these offers
and then use them to sell people on the
higher level and higher tier that you
have. Okay? And so people are not going
to become your client unless they trust
you. Now there is a chance that you can
build that trust through your social
media content. YouTube is another great
way to do this. some form of content
people are going to consume from you
where they're going to have to learn
something and then you have to give them
a direct call to action to what you have
for
sale. And chances are that you're not
just going to direct people to some kind
of a high ticket or mid-t membership
without them signing up for some kind of
a video presentation with you of some
kind. That's what I mentor all my
clients on is how to do these video
presentations in their coaching business
to get more clients, to get more people
buying from them. You know, you might
get the oneoff course or the one-off
sale, but to really scale to where you
have something that's sustainable,
that's not feast or famine, that's not
you just hoping that you can make enough
money to pay your bills or supplementing
your income. While that's great, I'm
talking about making something that
lasts, something that's of legacy, and
something that's going to really create
the kind of money that you want to make.
Having a consistent lead flow of some
kind is what is going to generate you
the kind of income that you want to
make. And so the best offers for that
are video offers. I meet a lot of people
they have they'll do ebook offers. I
recommend if you're doing an ebook, you
need to attach some kind of a 10-15
minute video to it. And in this video,
you're going to be able to break down
for them what are the goals, what is the
outcome that they're going to get out of
this. You can give some practical steps
of some things that they can do. You
teach them a little bit. But you got to
make sure that you are then selling them
something in that video. And if you do
this consistently and you get people to
consistently sign up for some kind of a
free offer, something that gives them
value, something that people would pay
money for. By the way, you give people
something that they would pay money for
that solves a problem, they will come
back to want to buy your paid thing,
your paid program. And what you want to
do is you want to make it to where it's
really not optional for them to buy your
paid program. Sure, of course, anybody
can have the option to buy or not. We're
not talking about holding a gun to
anybody's head. Don't be silly here. But
what I'm talking about is
that it becomes that it is the only path
to progress with you to truly get their
problem solved. As that if they want to
work with you to solve an actual problem
that you have, they need to buy the
program. They need to buy the training,
the course. And you got to raise your
prices on all of these things. If you're
charging
$1,000, that's good. $1,000 minimum for
a course is what you should be charging.
Now again, there's a difference between
low ticket courses and mid-tier courses
that are $1,000. A low ticket course, we
could sell that for seven bucks, 17
bucks. But the purpose behind a 17 or $7
course is as a marketing
tool to sell the higher level thing to
people. And that's how you're going to
be able to make the kind of money that
you want to make. not going to do volume
of low ticket stuff that's going to
actually make you the kind of money that
you want. You're going to ascend people
upwards to the higher tier, higher
ticket, higher level thing with you. And
that's what works the best right now.
And that's what we're seeing is working
the best right now. But video is the
thing that you got to do with people.
You have to connect via video with
people. I I have tried I have seen
clients that have tried without doing
video. they've done just ebooks to then
get a client. You got to have some form
of video presentation that creates that
connection. It's just not optional. And
so maybe you're not comfortable in front
of video. I get it. Not everybody is
right away. But the more you do it, the
more consistent you're going to get at
it and the more that you're going to
start to connect with the kind of people
that you want to connect with and you're
going to be able to build the kind of
business that you want to build. I'm not
perfect on my videos. My videos aren't
super polished. Heck, there's not even a
lot of editing at all. I I had one edit
in this whole video right here, this
whole podcast
episode, but I use it to connect with
people all the time and I have a seven
figureure business and I and I'm doing
everything perfect. Okay? So, follow
what I do. I could love to train you on
what I do. I'd love to show it to you.
I'd love for you to join my Wealthy
Coach Academy program. Actually, have a
14-day trial that you can try of that
program. I'd love to see you in there
and help you get the kind of results you
want to make inside your business. All
right, we'll talk soon. Grow your life.
Have a good one.
[Music]
[Applause]